<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<names>
	<namelist type="dat_TOTD">
		Tip 21:  Kill the Ancient Goblin Preist and forge the weapons near the Mines of Minoc,
		Tip 21:  Soulless Weapons can be found when killing Zombies in the Infected Lands,
		Tip 22:  Increased Stats and Skills between 2:00-4:00 and 11:00-12:00,
		Tip 21:  Vendors can be attacked.  Guards are killable.,
		Tip 21:  Stop by the Royal Casino in Britain.  Play cards and slot on the top of the bank while waiting for your friends.,
		Tip 20:  Grap a stick or sword and fight off the golbins invading the mining caves of Minoc.,
		Tip 20:  As you travel the land be careful as these poisonous patches may appear quickly before you. Take care to take with you many potions that cure. Learn the spells that will cure you and beware the poison of An Nox has returned.,
		Tip 19:  The cook needs more food for an upcoming festival. If you help him out he will reward you well. If your lucky have may give you one of three special gifts. Stop by the cooking guild in the tavern of Minoc and talk to the chef for more information.,
		Tip 18:  Try the Herbcraft system.  Seek out the plants of the world and collect spices and herbs to sell. Visit the wilder in Minoc,
		Tip 18:  Try the Witchcraft system.  Make magical food and spirits in the cauldren.  Visit the wicce in Minoc,
		Tip 17:  Free Mega Mount Mondays.  Visit the statue near the stables in Minoc for a change to get a ethereal mount.,
		Tip 16:  Free House Fridays.  Stop my the statues in Minoc on Friday to get a house deed.  One per adventure.,
		Tip 15:  Free Fantasy Swords on Super Sword Saturday.  A free weapon every hour.  Find the magic statue in Minoc.,
		Tip 14:  Type [CHAT to talk to other players.,
		Tip 13:  Travel north of Minoc to find the Pirate's Camp. These evil pirates will attack and fight. If you win you can take their bootee and sail the seas.,
		Tip 12:  Travel to Minoc to the house near the Tavern. Here you may seek out adventures and quests. Seek the QuestGiver. Talk to her. Ask her about a quest. Find the item of her desire and return it to her. Wealth will abound.,
		Tip 11:  When I was a child I would visit my Grandmother and we would play a game called Hide the Thimble. I would close my eyes and she would hide a sewing thimble somewhere in the room. I would search around as she would call out Cold Colder or Warm Warmer. When I would find the thimble I would return it to her for another try.  Grandma has since pasted however I have found memories of this game and hope to share the fun with you.,
		Tip 10:  The wandering bard has stopped by Ravon's Bar and Grill just north of Minoc. Stop in and listen to the wonderful old tells of Orcs Harpies and yours truely. Maybe the bard will sing a song about you.,
		Tip 9:  We have been decorating the Bank of Minoc. Stop by and see the new changes. Use the Waygate near by or train up with the stable near by.,
		Tip 8:  Visit the shrines of An Nox. Seek out the mystic armor of the shrine. Arms Of Compassion/Breastplate Of Justice/Cloak Of Humility/Dupres Shield/ Gauntlets Of Valor/Gorget Of Truth/Helm Of Spirituality/Legs Of Honor/Solaretes Of Sacrifice.  Collect the entire set of the Avatar.,
		Tip 7:  Can you laugh in the face of death? The Book of Kills is in your pack read it carefully. When you are not in An Nox visit our new Book of Kills website and see the wanted list. Then check out your own record with your very own page.,
		Tip 6:  You just missed another player! Our shard is small and I am sure you wish you knew when other players stopped by. Now you can. I have a special link so you can see who has been visiting An Nox.,
		Tip 5:  In an attempt to venture back to the good old days I am working towards building up Minoc Vesper and Britain in Felucca. I may add in Luna or move parts of it to one of these cities.,
		Tip 4:  All spawns have been removed from other parts of the world. Permanent spawns have been setup all over Felucca including the dungeons. Random spawns will be setup in the 3 cities and surrounding areas.,
		Tip 3: Travel quickly between these towns by using the 'WayGates'. These WayGates will take you from one town to the next. They can be found near the banks.,
		Tip 2: If you would like to stop by I usually visit around 10:00pm. Otherwise if you see me around I may be testing EasUO scripts.,
		Tip 1: Over in our forums check out our latest poll - Should An Nox included 'Reg Stones'? Your feedback is important.
	</namelist>
</names>