<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<names>
	<namelist type="dat_TOTD">
		Tip 1:  Travel to Minoc to the house near the Tavern. Here you may seek out adventures and quests. Seek the QuestGiver. Talk to her. Ask her about a quest. Find the item of her desire and return it to her. Wealth will abound.,
		Tip 2:  When I was a child I would visit my Grandmother and we would play a game called Hide the Thimble. I would close my eyes and she would hide a sewing thimble somewhere in the room. I would search around as she would call out Cold Colder or Warm Warmer. When I would find the thimble I would return it to her for another try.  Grandma has since pasted however I have found memories of this game and hope to share the fun with you.,
		Tip 3:  The wandering bard has stopped by Ravon's Bar and Grill just north of Minoc. Stop in and listen to the wonderful old tells of Orcs Harpies and yours truely. Maybe the bard will sing a song about you.,
		Tip 4:  We have been decorating the Bank of Minoc. Stop by and see the new changes. Use the Waygate near by or train up with the stable near by.,
		Tip 5:  Visit the shrines of An Nox. Seek out the mystic armor of the shrine. Arms Of Compassion/Breastplate Of Justice/Cloak Of Humility/Dupres Shield/ Gauntlets Of Valor/Gorget Of Truth/Helm Of Spirituality/Legs Of Honor/Solaretes Of Sacrifice.  Collect the entire set of the Avatar.,
		Tip 6:  Can you laugh in the face of death? The Book of Kills is in your pack read it carefully. When you are not in An Nox visit our new Book of Kills website and see the wanted list. Then check out your own record with your very own page.,
		Tip 7:  You just missed another player! Our shard is small and I am sure you wish you knew when other players stopped by. Now you can. I have a special link so you can see who has been visiting An Nox.,
		Tip 8:  In an attempt to venture back to the good old days I am working towards building up Minoc Vesper and Britain in Felucca. I may add in Luna or move parts of it to one of these cities.,
		Tip 9:  All spawns have been removed from other parts of the world. Permanent spawns have been setup all over Felucca including the dungeons. Random spawns will be setup in the 3 cities and surrounding areas.,
		Tip 10: Travel quickly between these towns by using the 'WayGates'. These WayGates will take you from one town to the next. They can be found near the banks.,
		Tip 11: If you would like to stop by I usually visit around 10:00pm. Otherwise if you see me around I may be testing EasUO scripts.,
		Tip 12: Over in our forums check out our latest poll - Should An Nox included 'Reg Stones'? Your feedback is important.
	</namelist>
</names>